<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<courses>
  <course id="1">
    <title>Bachelor of Information Management (BIM)</title>
    <level>Undergraduate</level>
    <duration>4 Years</duration>
    <seats>60</seats>
    <affiliation>Tribhuvan University</affiliation>
    <eligibility>10+2 or equivalent with minimum 45% in any stream</eligibility>
    <fee>NPR 1,20,000/year</fee>
    <description>A four-year program blending IT skills with management principles, preparing students for careers in IT management, systems analysis, and digital business.</description>
    <subjects>Database Management, Web Technologies, E-Commerce, MIS, Programming, Business Communication</subjects>
    <career>IT Manager, Systems Analyst, Database Admin, Web Developer, Business Analyst</career>
  </course>
  <course id="2">
    <title>Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)</title>
    <level>Undergraduate</level>
    <duration>4 Years</duration>
    <seats>60</seats>
    <affiliation>Tribhuvan University</affiliation>
    <eligibility>10+2 or equivalent with minimum 45% in any stream</eligibility>
    <fee>NPR 1,10,000/year</fee>
    <description>A comprehensive business program covering finance, marketing, HRM, and entrepreneurship to develop future business leaders.</description>
    <subjects>Principles of Management, Financial Accounting, Marketing, Business Law, HRM, Entrepreneurship</subjects>
    <career>Business Manager, Marketing Executive, HR Officer, Entrepreneur, Financial Analyst</career>
  </course>
  <course id="3">
    <title>Bachelor of Science in CSIT</title>
    <level>Undergraduate</level>
    <duration>4 Years</duration>
    <seats>48</seats>
    <affiliation>Tribhuvan University</affiliation>
    <eligibility>10+2 Science with Mathematics, minimum 45%</eligibility>
    <fee>NPR 1,30,000/year</fee>
    <description>A technology-focused degree offering strong foundations in programming, algorithms, networking, and software engineering.</description>
    <subjects>C Programming, Data Structures, OOP, Operating Systems, Computer Networks, Software Engineering</subjects>
    <career>Software Developer, Network Engineer, Data Scientist, System Administrator, IT Consultant</career>
  </course>
  <course id="4">
    <title>Master of Business Administration (MBA)</title>
    <level>Postgraduate</level>
    <duration>2 Years</duration>
    <seats>40</seats>
    <affiliation>Pokhara University</affiliation>
    <eligibility>Bachelor degree in any discipline with minimum 50%</eligibility>
    <fee>NPR 2,20,000/year</fee>
    <description>An advanced management program designed for professionals seeking to enhance leadership capabilities and strategic thinking in global business.</description>
    <subjects>Strategic Management, Corporate Finance, Operations Management, Business Research, Leadership</subjects>
    <career>CEO, COO, Management Consultant, Director, Senior Manager</career>
  </course>
</courses>
